{
    "id": "5d7dc06ebef640a09cb848229a0843b3",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… Joe in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2285dcf3488d4ebaa2039668a32c6fa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. recognize me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "doesn't",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00feb20f5a9f4ee2a4f68057651cb2c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… out of the window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has looked",
                "looked",
                "had looked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c0e72e47fcf4daba63386cae536d6d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter ………………. another window yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was breaking",
                "broke",
                "has broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb6eb1c23a2544debee8cd4052ddf6b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Deceived by his friends, he ………………. all hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "has lost",
                "had lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d5893587b9c424d9f5bb76d5c622836"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………… the boy for misbehaving in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has punished",
                "punished",
                "had punished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9d4f4e5babf46be8766fcf407d064a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat …………….. all the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had drunk",
                "has drunk",
                "drank"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a0b022e012df466cb09fe6ac7fe867ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bell ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rung",
                "has rung",
                "rang"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8eabd9e243bf400c9b04550c4c1560e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sailor ……………….. with the sinking ship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has stayed",
                "had stayed",
                "stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3ae35c503d294cdea99b212e111a2a9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………. if he could have another piece of cake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has asked",
                "asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52707fca95894becb221a2411cafd8c4"
        }
    ]
}